social9.com 2017-07-13

# Privacy - Social9

**Introduction**

We respect your privacy, and want to ensure the best experience while interacting with Social9 (“we” or “us”), while using our services (“Social9 Services”, “Social9 Widget” or “Social9 Platform” ), or browsing our website www.social9.com (“Website”, or “Social9 Website”), including the internal dashboard provided to our Customers. Social9 Services are deployed on our Customers’ web or mobile applications (“Customer Web Applications” or “Customer Websites”) and is used by our Customers’ online users (“End-Users”).

This Privacy Policy describes how we collect, use, and disclose the Personal and non-Personal Information of our customers and End-Users (as defined below) on the Social9 Website and through Social9’ Services.

This Privacy Policy is incorporated to and is subject to the Social9 Terms of Use, and any capitalized terms not defined herein will have the meaning provided in our Terms of Use. By using Social9’ Website or Services, you consent to the use of your Personal Information as described in this Privacy Policy.

 **Operation of Social9 Website**

The Social9 website has three key purposes : i) Providing information on our products, services, and on technical support and resources, ii) as a key channel of communication, and iii) providing access to the Social9 Dashboard to let our Customers manage their Social9 account and configurations. During the operation of the Website, we may collect your personal information via various channels such as contact forms, live chats, account creation, etc.

 **Operation of Social9 Services**

Social9 Services are delivered to our Customers and their End-Users users via our turnkey plugins and HTML code on our Customers’ web applications. In order to provide these services, Social9 may collect some Non-Personal Information of the End-Users on behalf of our Customers. The collected information is owned by Social9 and that Customer, and will be used as per this Privacy Policy, as well as per our Customer’s privacy policy.

 **Information We Collect**

We aim to collect and use such information as is required to enable us to manage our Customer accounts, provide Social9 Services, maintain our Customer/visitor lists, respond to inquiries or provide feedback, for identification and authentication purposes, and for service improvements. We will only use your Personal Information for the purposes for which they were collected.

Two types of information may be collected through the Website and our Services: Personal Information and Non-Personal Information. This Privacy Policy does not extend to the collection, use, or disclosure of the following information which is currently not limited by applicable privacy laws: (a) information that is publicly available, such as names, addresses, telephone numbers, and electronic addresses when listed in a directory or made available through directory assistance; or (b) Non-Personal Information (as defined further below).

“ _Personal Information_ ” is personally identifiable information, such as your name, address, email address, credit card information, birth date, and gender. At the time of collection, we will clearly identify the information being collected and the purposes for which it will be used. It is always the Customer’s choice whether or not to provide Personal Information, but if the Customer chooses not to provide certain requested Personal Information, in some instances the Customer may not be able to register to use the Website, or be able to access and use the Website at all. 

In other instances, the Customers’ choice not to provide certain Personal Information may mean that the Customer will not be able to use certain features of the Website or the Service. We may collect Personal Information through registration processes, communications with the Customer, information downloads, service use, user support, and surveys.

“ _Non-Personal Information_ ” is information of an anonymous nature, such as an Internet Protocol Address (IP Address), the domain used to access the Website, and the type and version of browser or operating system being used by visitors to the website. Aggregate information, such as demographic statistics of our users (e.g. average age or geographical allocation of our users), number of visitors, what pages users access or visit, and average time spent on the Website is not considered Personal Information.

Such Non-Personal Information may be collected by Social9 in the course of operating the Website. For example, our web servers may automatically collect Non-Personal Information that is provided through your browser or stored in a cookie when you choose to visit the Website.

 **How We Use the Information that We Collect**

We may use the information (Personal as well as Non-Personal) in the following ways:

  1. We will use your email address to contact you about important information or notices about Social9 or to respond to your queries. We may display your name, email address, and other information within your Social9 account as well as other sections of the website. It will only be viewable to you.
  2. We may use non-personally identifiable information to statistically analyze our web and business performances. This helps us to enhance your experience with our services.
  3. If you write a testimonial for us and give us consent to publish it, we may display your name, title, and company on our testimonial section. We never disclose or share any information which identifies you personally with any third party. (Please see below disclosure for further details.)
  4. End-User information is used to deliver services to our Customers, provide analytics, and other services. Our Customers own that information.

 **When We Disclose Information**

Social9 does not share, sell, or rent your information to any third party website or company. We may require disclosing your personal information to respond to legal requirements, to enforce our policies, to respond to claims that you or use of service by you violates another’s rights, or to protect anyone’s rights, property, or safety.

 **Security**

Any personal data you provide us is securely stored in a database which only a few authorized employees can access. The server holding your personal data is protected against unauthorized physical as well as electronic access. These measures include an electronic firewall and various other protection measures that involve virus scanning, installation of security patches, vulnerability testing, backup, recovery planning, employee training, security audits, and other steps designed to constantly improve the data protection procedures. The server is not directly connected to the internet and data is therefore available only to authorized computers. However, Social9 cannot assure full security as it is not possible to make a system 100% secure in practice.

 **Your Rights**

You can ask us to correct and, where relevant, erase your information. Please note that certain Personal Information may need to be retained by Social9 for a period of time. This is necessary for legitimate business purposes and required or authorized by applicable law. As mentioned above you have a right to change your Personal Information at any time by logging into your Social9 dashboard or by sending us an email.

 **Business Relationships with Social Share Networks**

Social9 may have business relations (or partnerships) with some social share networks such as Google, Facebook, Pinterest, etc. However, we are not responsible for the terms of use and privacy policies for any of these social share networks. Please visit their websites for more information about their privacy policies and terms of use.

 **Changes to This Privacy Policy**

We may update this Privacy Policy by posting a new version on our website. This helps you to always be aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, it is disclosed.

 **Contact and Questions**

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please contact:

Email: legal [at] social9 [dot] com
